So let's just have
this in our hands
while we're listening and
thinking about things,
and let me just tell
you about this one way--
if I take a piece of glass--
if I take a piece of
glass, and now imagine
that I take some part of
it, like this part here.
And in this part I'm
going to cool faster,
and in this part here
I'm going to cool slower.
So imagine it's a slab of glass,
and it's like the edges are
cooled at a different rate.
That's actually exactly
why a car window,
if you look at it through
polarized glasses,
has spots on it.
Those spots, some of
you may have seen these.
Those spots are changes,
purposeful changes
in the mechanical properties
of the glass to keep you safe.
Why?
If you call it slower, then
you might have some volume
that you want.
The volume here, let's call
this Vb and let's call this Va.
That goes along with the
graph we used before, b and a.
So it wants V--
what did I do-- b.
This wants Va.
But look at what happens.